healthcareitnews.com 2019-05-30

# Privacy Policy | Healthcare IT News

To receive the monthly _Healthcare IT News_ issues or our email newsletters, or to access downloadable content such as white papers or register for online events such as webinars, you must first complete a registration form. During registration for newsletters and print issues, you may be required to give contact information such as name, email address and telephone number. We use this information to contact you about the services and newsletters on our site in which you have expressed interest.

The information helps us provide you with access to a wide variety of content on our site and better serve you through customized newsletters and other products. _Healthcare IT News_ shares aggregate, non-personally identifying data with our partners and advertisers. We disclose website usage information to third parties only in aggregate.

We may make email and mailing addresses of registrants available to carefully screened businesses that provide products or services that we think may be of interest. If you do not want to receive email or USPS-mailed offers from our advertising or conference partners please send an email stating this preference and including your full name and address to [healthcareitnews@halldata.com](mailto:healthcareitnews@halldata.com). Or, please call 1-847-763-9618.

_Healthcare IT News_ will NEVER share your phone or fax number with ANY third party. You may receive email, telephone or fax communications from _Healthcare IT News_ regarding your subscription or for research purposes. Please see our registration page (<http://healthcareitnews.com/register?return2url=%2F>) for further details.

All email sent by HIMSS Media includes a clear opt-out button in the footer of the email. If you want to opt-out of receiving email from HIMSS Media, please click that link and complete the process.

_Healthcare IT News_ does assign a cookie to each site visitor so we can identify users who return to the website. This cookie is used only to track unique visitors to the site and to assist in making more accurate content recommendations.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this site are delivered to you by 24/7 RealMedia's Open AdStream, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Surveys or Contests**

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to notify contest winners, award prizes and send other forms of communication, such as email newsletters, from _Healthcare IT News_. If we also provide information to research sponsors, we will let you know when we request information from you. We use may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

**Commenting Policy**

SIte users are encouraged to post comments on _Healthcare IT News_ content including stories and blogs. Our site uses the popular commenting service Disqus.  This service allows users to post comments by signing in using an existing Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google Plus or Disqus account. _Healthcare IT News_ does not obtain any information about or access to your accounts with these services.  For more information about Disqus' privacy policy, please [click here](http://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy).

Comments should be editorial in nature, and should not be promoting or otherwise linking to third party products or websites. The use of all-caps, text markup or other methods of "shouting" are discouraged in the interest of maintaining a high-level, respectful forum for discussion.

Comments may not:

  * Insult, antagonize or otherwise offend other site users or editors
  * Contain obscene, racist, sexist, defamatory, hateful, distasteful or otherwise inappropriate language
  * Contain libelous statements
  * Contain promotional materials, advertisements or press announcements
  * Contain any other material that inhibits the ability of other users to enjoy our site.

Provided that all efforts are made by site users to self-edit and employ respectful language that does not antagonize other site users, comments may:

  * Actively engage other readers and our editors in thoughtful discussion
  * Give constructive feedback on article accuracy or informed commentary on article content
  * Ask questions of other readers and editors.

Site administrators reserve the right to delete comments and permanently block users who fail to adhere to the commenting policy, even upon a first offense.

**Promotions**

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and white papers. We allow you to opt-out of these types of communications.

**Webinars and White Papers**

By accessing a webinar or white paper content asset, you agree to your contact information being supplied to the sponsor of that content asset. Only the information that you have supplied will be sent to the sponsor. Once you provide your contact information through our form, your information will be supplied to that sponsor even if you have previously opted out of receiving information from HIMSS Media sponsors.

**Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. Your use of our website indicates to us that you have read and accepted our privacy policy. This policy is subject to change. We will change the date on this page noting when the policy was last updated. If you have questions or comments on this privacy policy, we would like to hear them. Please email us at: editor@healthcareitnews.com
